Christopher Metcalf

Software Engineer

27 Park Ave, Northwood, NH 03261 **Cell: (603) 325-3698**

christopher.metcalf@proton.me
https://github.com/C-Metcalf

SUMMARY

Proficient mid-level software developer with two years of experience in designing, developing, and deploying software applications. Utilizing Django, Python, and PyQt to write simple, secure, and scalable code. Successfully redesigned the company's website, product line, in house software, and infrastructure.

Languages

Python

C++

Ruby

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

EXPERIENCE

National Aperture Inc, Salem, NH — *Software Engineer*

October 2022 — present

Responsible for developing and implementing software applications

- Create & maintain website utilizing Django, DRF, & PostgreSQL
- Communications via UART, USB, I2C, SPI and CAN
- Front-end web development with Ruby on Rails & Tailwind
- GUI App development for Raspberry Pi using Qt/Pyside6

Frameworks

Django

PyQt

Rails

Aldi, Concord — store associate

February 2020 – October 2022

- Coordinated with a small team to work efficiently
- Was recommended for manager position
- Worked with heavy machinery
- Handle large sums of cash daily
- Opened and closed the store regularly

Databases

PostgreSQL

MariaDB

MySQL

EDUCATION

Associate's in Computer Engineering & Technology

January 2021 - May 2023, New Hampshire Technical Institute